Are... are you all right?
هل .. هل أنت بخير؟
Yes, Ziying.
نعم ، زيينغ.
Wipe your face by yourself, then.
امسح وجهك بنفسك ، إذن.
Ziying,
تسيينغ ،
I'm hurt.
أنا أتألم.
Do you still have the heart to let me do it myself?
هل ما زلت تملك القلب للسماح لي بالقيام بذلك بنفسي؟
Stay away.
ابق بعيدا.
Mm.
مم.
Do not move.
لا تتحرك.
Hold still.
اثبت.
♪Memories are fading♪
الذكريات تتلاشى
♪Sweetness peels off the past♪
حلاوة تقشر من الماضي ♪
♪A mess is left behind♪
خلفك فوضى
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP3= =Approaching Her Will Bring Misfortune=
= EP3 = = الاقتراب منها سيجلب لها سوء الحظ =
(Where am I again?)
(أين أنا مرة أخرى؟)
(How did I get here?)
(كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟)
Su Ziying?
سو زيينغ؟
Why is it you again?
لماذا أنت مرة أخرى؟
This is my stop.
هذه محطتي.
I should get off.
يجب أن أنزل.
(What exactly is this all about?)
(ما هو بالضبط كل هذا؟)
Why do I do weird things
لماذا أفعل أشياء غريبة
every time I meet her?
في كل مرة أقابلها؟
Did she
هل فعلت
do witchcraft on me?
تفعل السحر علي؟
I'll bewitch you and suck your soul.
سوف أسحرك وأمتص روحك.
Or...
أو...
Did she poison me?
هل سممتني؟
Eat this apple
كل هذه التفاحة
and you'll forget everything
وستنسى كل شيء
and become an idiot.
وتصبح أحمق.
She's so malicious.
إنها خبيثة للغاية.
And she's violent.
وهي عنيفة.
Violent?
عنيف؟
I'm sure it's her fault.
أنا متأكد من أنه خطأها.
She slapped me so that I fell sick.
صفعتني حتى مرضت.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
I have to
على أن
stay
يقضي
away
بعيد
from her.
منها.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Without that guy...
بدون هذا الرجل ...
I would nearly...
أود تقريبا ...
(Apple?)
(تفاحة؟)
(Witch.)
(ساحرة.)
(Why is it her again?)
(لماذا هي مرة أخرى؟)
(She really haunts.)
(إنها تطارد حقًا.)
Su Ziying?
سو زيينغ؟
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
why are you avoiding me?
لماذا تتجنبني
I just don't want to see you.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أراك.
You don't want to see me?
انت لا تريد ان تراني؟
I think you just want to welch on my pay.
أعتقد أنك تريد فقط أن أتحمل راتبي.
As defined in the tenth clause
على النحو المحدد في الفقرة العاشرة
of the Contract Law of the People's Republic of China,
من قانون العقود لجمهورية الصين الشعبية ،
a contract is established
تم إنشاء العقد
in written,
مكتوبة،
(Related Regulations of Civil Code and Authoritative Cases)
(اللوائح ذات الصلة من القانون المدني والقضايا الرسمية)
oral, or other forms.
عن طريق الفم ، أو أشكال أخرى.
All forms of contracts
جميع أنواع العقود
shall have the same legal effect.
يجب أن يكون لها نفس الأثر القانوني.
You!
أنت!
The electricity went out.
انقطعت الكهرباء.
I'll go check it out.
سأذهب للتحقق من ذلك.
Don't leave.
لا ترحل.
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
you can't be afraid of the dark, can you?
لا يمكنك أن تخاف من الظلام ، أليس كذلك؟
♪My love don't ever leave me♪
♪ حبي لا يتركني أبدًا
♪Tonight I'll leave an exclusive mark on you♪
♪ الليلة سأترك بصمة حصرية عليك
♪Let's go I plan to sneak into your dream♪
♪ دعنا نذهب وأنا أخطط للتسلل إلى حلمك ♪
♪Turn into the angle and devil and be the only love in your heart♪
♪ استدر إلى الزاوية والشيطان وكن الحب الوحيد في قلبك
(We're sometimes stuck in the dark.)
(نحن في بعض الأحيان عالقون في الظلام.)
(But there's always somebody)
(لكن هناك دائما شخص ما)
(who'll walk you through when you're lost.)
(من سيرشدك عندما تضيع).
(Because of this person,)
(بسبب هذا الشخص)
(even the darkness)
(حتى الظلام)
(seems to grow tender.)
(يبدو أنه ينمو.)
(I think)
(أظن)
(this is the light.)
(هذا هو الضوء).
(Who's the light for you?)
(من هو النور لك؟)
♪I hold your hand the next second oh♪
♪ أمسك يدك في الثانية التالية أوه ♪
♪My love my love♪
♪ حبيبي حبي ♪
♪You lay claim to my heart♪
أنت تدعي قلبي ♪
♪I never mean to run away♪
♪ لا أقصد أبدا الهروب
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)